

CONTACT

PHONE: (831)-324-8537

WESBITES:

https://aeuler.github.io/webPortfolio/

https://spot-on-weather.com/

https://www.vbsurfrescuemuseum.org

https://aeuler.vb-atc.com/cumulusshoe-service/

EMAIL:

andreweuler01@gmail.com

BACKGROUND

An experienced individual in Networking, Cybersecurity, and Web Development.

During my high school tenure, I attended both Salem High School and the Advanced Technology Center.

At the Advanced Technology Center, I took Network Administration and Cybersecurity I, Network Administration and Cybersecurity II, and Advanced Web Design.

At Salem High School, I took numerous AP related courseware. One highly important course, AP Computer Science A, is where I learned the fundamentals of Java.

ANDREW EULER

Networking, Cybersecurity, Web Development

EDUCATION

Salem High School

06/2018 – 06/2022 3.92529 GPA; Advanced Studies Diploma

Advanced Technology Center

09/2019 - 06/2022 4.0 GPA

Tidewater Community College

06/2022 – 06/2024 TBD

WORK EXPERIENCE

Virginia Beach Surf & Rescue Museum Web Developer Intern 06/2022–Present

- Participation in scheduled meetings with Museum Representative and staff
- Creating social media posts in cooperation with museum staff
- Update navigation bar and add pages as is necessary
- Log all hours and submit upon request
- Provide input into page management
- Provide suggestions for updating the website

ATC NTHS Historian / Secretary

09/2020-06/2022

- Led 3 inductions (1 virtual; 2 in-person) with fellow office members
- Contributed to community service project
- Took attendance & led meetings with fellow office members

Salem NHS Serviceship

09/2020-06/2022

 Volunteered 41.5 hours through NHS-sponsored activities during the 2021-2022 school year.

NAS Oceana Base Chapel Bible Study Assistant

07/2017-07/2019

 Volunteered over 60 hours mentoring younger students at local Vacation Bible School.

SKILLS

- Linux, Windows Server
- Networking, Cybersecurity
- HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Java,
- Bootstrap
- WordPress
- Wix
- Weebly
- Square Online
- MS Office (Word, PowerPoint, Excel, etc.)

ATC Future Business Leaders of America (FBLA)

Salem Scholars

Member

• Salem NHS member

 ATC National Technical Honor Society (NTHS)

Salem Rho Kappa Charter

AWARDS

ACTIVITIES

- AP Computer Science A
 Academic Excellence Award
- ODU, WHRO, CII Great Computer Challenge (GCC) 2nd place team in Web Design
- Earth Science Academic Excellence Award
- Visual and Performing Arts Academy (VPAA)
 Sportsmanship Award
- Salem Student of the Month for March 2019

CERTIFICATIONS

- Workplace Readiness Skills
- MTA 98-366: Networking Fundamentals
- MTA 98-367: Security Fundamentals
- CompTIA Network+
- CompTIA Security+
- MTA 98-382: Introduction to Programming Using JavaScript
- MTA 98-383: Introduction to Programming Using HTML & CSS
- W3schools R Fundamentals
- Google IT Support Professional
- IBM Cybersecurity Analyst Professional
- Google Fundamentals of Digital Marketing
- Google Ads Search
- Google Ads Display
- AWS Cloud Practitioner Essentials
- AWS Technical Essentials